Yes, I am the Director of the Village Star of Ugka.
Let's start the second part.
The reason why I decided to become an idol is because when I was in the 4th grade of elementary school, Kanako Momota of Momoshiki Clover Z came to my elementary school,
I heard her say that we should work together to achieve our various dreams,
That's how I got my dream of becoming an entertainer when I was in the 5th grade of elementary school,
I wanted to join Stardust Promotion, where Kanako Momota is a member.
I heard that there was an audition for new members of Sakura Ebies, so I decided to apply for it.
I really, really love Kanako, and if it weren't for her, I wouldn't be here now.
I think it's the moment when I'm standing on the stage.
When I see everyone calling out my name or calling out my name and having fun together...
I always feel that I am glad to be an idol.
The thing that made me happy when I was told by fans was
I'm really happy with all the words you write to me.
They really touch my heart.
When I'm feeling a little down, or when I write a story or a sentence
When I write a story or a sentence like that
I feel that it's okay for you to stay the same.
You don't have to change.
I was happy when you told me that I don't have to change.
Q. What is the member's color?
I don't have a member color, but it's unofficial,
I like blue because I like blue,
I like the color blue, and the people who are my friends wave blue penlights at me during the live,
I also have a towel with my name written on it,
I would be very happy if you could wear them on your T-shirts,
I would be happy if you could wear them.
Q. What are the members' colors?
It's cute.
If I had to describe it in one word, it would be "power.
The reason for this is that I think we put a lot of effort into our performances,
I chose "power" because I think we are putting a lot of effort into our performances, and because Uka has been around for 8 years this year, and I think we are working hard with a lot of bottom-up energy.
Q. What is your goal for this year?
Ucka's songs have a wide range of high and low tones in one song,
I think this is true for other groups as well,
There are also a lot of changes in formation positions,
I think that the many changes in the position of the formation and the many details of the dance are the points where we cannot be outdone.
The live performance that left the greatest impression on me was the "All Out Second" live performance of all the songs held in November last year.
It wasn't my first time, but it was my second time.
It was the first time, not the first time, but the second time,
This time we performed 44 songs,
It was not my first time, but it was my second time.
As for the performance, first of all, I think the quality of my voice itself has changed,
I used to be told that my dancing was too stiff and that my shoulders were too high,
I was warned that my dancing was too stiff and my shoulders were too high, but I don't get that anymore,
Fans also noticed that my eyes were swimming a lot,
When I was younger, I was often told that my eyes would swim and I would get worried,
But recently they have told me that I look very confident.
I think that's what has changed.
What is your favorite song to play live?
Any questions?
In terms of singing, there has been a song called "Shining City Lights,
This song is my featured song,
I sing the beginning, the chorus, and the highest part of the song,
It's a song where I sing the highest part of the song, such as the beginning and the chorus,
I sing the highest part in the solo part, which is not the highest part in any of Uguka's songs,
I struggled a lot with that part.
I did it.
Oh! Well then...
Well, five songs, huh? Okay, then.
The first one is the first song.
A song called "Imaginary Travel
and the second song is called
Shining City Lights
and the third song is Cosmic Float
and the fourth song is called
The fourth song is
Wonder Little Love
and the last song is called Growing Up Days.
It's my favorite song.
As for the costumes, lately I've been wearing long skirts and white outfits.
So I thought I'd wear something cool, like short shorts or a black outfit with a little bit of sparkle.
I'd like to wear a cool outfit that's a little bit black and shiny.
I wonder what I'd like to do at award shows... I've done a lot of award shows in the past, but I'm not sure what I'd like to do.
I've done a lot of different kinds of award shows in the past, but recently I've been doing online award shows, where I usually sign and date photos and stuff.
I usually sign and date photos or something like that, but recently I've been doing online benefit events.
I would like to hold an award event where I write a message or two or three to the person who purchased the photo.
As I mentioned earlier, the group as a whole has many formation changes,
As I mentioned earlier, the group as a whole has a lot of formation changes, and our dances can be quite cool or detailed,
Also, I would like the audience to see the wide range of high and low tones in the songs, and personally, I think the songs have a lot to offer,
Personally, I am very conscious of the details of the song, even down to the tips of the hands,
I was also told by my dance instructor that I should dance all the way up to the skirt since the skirt is long now.
Well, what kind of work do you do if you are not in it by accident?
Well, I have always wanted to work as a model.
I think I might have been aiming for that kind of job.
Oh, if you are not in the entertainment industry...
When I was in elementary school, I dreamed of being a baker.
I don't know...
I really like melon bread, and not only melon bread, but I like bread so much that I have bread for breakfast every day.
I wonder if I am a baker.
I would like to enter Igirinari Tohoku-san.
I would like to join Tohoku-san and sing some songs with them.
If I have never done anything before, I would like to work as a model,
I would also like to try my hand at illustration, and maybe do some work that is not manga, but drawing pictures.
I haven't talked to Sora yet,
I haven't told Sora yet, but we went out for dinner in March,
Sora invited me to have dinner with him,
Sora invited me to dinner, so we went to have okonomiyaki,
Normally, I would have taken a picture when the okonomiyaki arrived or when the food was served,
But we were too hungry and ate first,
It was surreal to take pictures after we had finished eating everything.It was surreal to take pictures after we had finished eating everything.
It was fun talking to you the whole time.
My goal for the next 10 years is to be 30.
Thirty, but I've always dreamed of being in the entertainment industry since I was in the fifth grade.
I have always dreamed of entering the entertainment industry.
I have always had a dream of entering the entertainment industry since I was in the 5th grade of elementary school, so I hope to continue in the entertainment industry.
Also, when I am 30 years old...
I also hope to have a car license when I am 30 years old.
Thank you very much.
What should I do?
I'd like to answer the last question, "Do you have a secret favorite place that you don't really want to share with anyone?
I write about where I've been and what I've done every day on my Instagram story.
I write about where I went and what I did every day on my Instagram story, so I've already told a lot of people.
It's not that I don't want to tell you, but I like coffee shops and such.
I like coffee shops and I feel at home there, so I go there a lot.
I say "quite a lot" a lot, and it's become a habit of mine, but I spend a lot of time there.
After that, no problem.
I say "quite a lot" again. I say it a lot. I say it a lot. I'm sorry, I'd like to visit coffee shops and so on.
Lastly, I'd like to make an announcement from Ukka.
Uca's major label first single "wonder little love" was released on June 21.
Thank you very much.
Yes, that's right.
The name of the first single is "wonder little love", so I'd like to recommend the title track, "wonder little love", which directly translates to "mysterious little love". The song is designed to uplift the excitement and anticipation of the budding of this mysterious little love, and you can say "Wonderful little love" together in the chorus,
I think the song is easy to remember, so I hope you will enjoy it.
Next, let's continue,
We have three solo live concerts scheduled for this year and next year.
On Saturday, September 30, I will be performing at Shibuya Beats.
On Saturday, October 14, I will perform at Tokyo Kinema Club.
And on Sunday, January 21, next year, at Ebisu Liquid Room,
Uguka's one-man live performance is scheduled for January 21, 2012 at Ebisu Liquid Room.
If you are interested, please come and see us. We look forward to seeing you there.
The point I would like you to pay attention to is this,
Each and every one of them is really showing various ways of performing,
I think that each one of us has a different way of showing our performance,
I've seen it in the dance teacher's lessons,
I have even had dance teachers tell me to lift up my chin and put more pressure on it,
I've learned a lot from my dance teacher,
I have learned a lot from my dance teachers,
So each and every one of us dances with that in mind,
We all dance with these things in mind, and in our singing, we sing with a passion to convey our message to everyone who comes to see us.
I really hope you will come and enjoy the show.
And one more thing, I, Director Murahoshi, am going to perform in Tokyo Yomarenland vol.3 "Uguisudari no Bara" at Tokyo Kinenba Club on Wednesday, September 6.
I will be performing in "Uguisudari no Roses" at the Tokyo Kinenba Club on Wednesday, September 6th.
Thank you very much.
I'm really very, very happy.
I'm very happy and I'm very excited because I've heard that Tokyo Night Land is a live concert with lots of activities such as acting, singing, dancing and talking.
I'm looking forward to creating a stage together with other groups, and I'll do my best to bring a fun time to everyone, so please come and enjoy the show.
Oh! I've played a teacher on the radio before, in a sort of radio drama, on the Uguka radio, so I wonder what kind of role I'll be playing.
I was wondering what kind of role I would like to play. I would like to play a boyish character.
The question and answer session is now over.
Thank you very much for all the questions.
Thank you very much for your time and for watching the show so far.
Please come and see us at our solo live, release event, and many more!
That's all for now. Thank you very much.